supersentai.com 2013-08-05

# Power Rangers Central / Privacy Policy

---  
| 

Super Sentai Time Capsule has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and spreading practices for this Web site: Super Sentai Time Capsule

  Personal Information  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

  What do you do with the information collected?  
All information collected will be used solely by Power Rangers Central and not given, sold, or otherwise transferred to third parties in a personally identifiable form.

Use of Cookies  
Power Rangers Central may make use of cookies (small pieces of information placed on your computer by our website) for information collection purposes. Any information provided by these cookies will not be personally identifiable and is solely used to improve your experience at our site. We dot not passively connect personally identifiable information through the use of cookies.

  External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. Super Sentai Time Capsule is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Third Party Cookies

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, feel free to contact us at 

[webmaster@rangercentral.com](mailto:webmaster@rangercentral.com?subject=To%20Webmaster%20of%20PRC). 

|
